topic = "Substitute underlied word with a synonym.";
cards = [
 {"question":"I see a _big_(330th) house across the street",
  "answer": ["huge", "giant", "enormous", "monstrous", "large", "gigantic", "giant-size"],
  "question_word": "big"
 },
 {"question":"I see a _high_(164th) office building",
  "answer": ["big", "tall", "towering", "colossal", "giant", "gigantic", "monstrous"],
  "question_word": "high"
 },
 {"question":"I see a _small_(th) house",
  "answer": ["little", "tiny"],
  "question_word": "small"
 },
 {"question":"Did you see _slow_(th) this car is?",
  "answer": ["unrushed"],
  "question_word": "slow"
 },
 {"question":"A girl rides a _horse_",
  "answer": ["pony", "destoryer", "hack", "nag"],
  "question_word": "horse"
 },
 {"question":"She was very _happy_ that day",
  "answer": ["in a good mood", "cheerful", "glad", "satisfied"],
  "question_word": "happy"
 },
 {"question":"She was very _unhappy_ that day",
  "answer": ["in a bad mood", "gloomy", "unsatisfied"],
  "question_word": "happy"
 },
 {"question":"This job was _good_",
  "answer": ["well-done", "high quality"],
  "question_word": "good"
 },
 {"question":"This job was _bad_",
  "answer": ["nasty", "poor quality"],
  "question_word": "bad"
 },
 {"question":"I am a _good_ person",
  "answer": ["kind", "honest"],
  "question_word": "good"
 },
 {"question":"I am a _bad_ person",
  "answer": ["mean", "nasty", "naughty"],
  "question_word": "bad"
 },
 {"question":"I heard a _talk_ the other day between crew",
  "answer": ["gossip"],
  "question_word": "talk"
 },
 {"question":"I see these _beautiful_ flowers",
  "answer": ["good-looking"],
  "question_word": "beautiful"
 },
 {"question":"I see this _ugly_ house",
  "answer": ["bad-looking", "creepy"],
  "question_word": "ugly"
 },
 {"question":"You are _fast_.",
  "answer": ["quick"],
  "question_word": "fast"
 },
 {"question":"This picture is very _colorful_",
  "answer": ["vivid"],
  "question_word": "colorful"
 },
]

include("js/engine.js",function(){
  //
});